

DMYTRO RIABTSUN

Phone: +38063 217-41-91

E-mail: riabtsun@i.ua

LinkedIn /riabtsun

telegram: @revuchiy

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hi, my name is Dmytro, and I'm learning front-end development So far, I'm interested in all that will help to better master this profession. Stubborn and motivated to develop my skills and abilities to grow professionally. I love turning layouts into websites. I have theoretical and practical experience in the front-end that is necessary for a successful start in this position.

In my free time I like to play with friends in a band, or spend time on walks.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FE DEVELOPER

Twigel tech (2020 - 2021)

- Work with CMS, Shopware 6
- Restyling default themes
- Creating custom CMS blocks/elements
- Changing layots on TWIG

WEB DEVELOPER

BaDM (2021 - present)

- Website creation on wordpress
- Company website administration

SKILLS

- Javascript
- Basic knowledge about jquery
- git (gitlab, github)
- HTML/CSS
- SASS, Bootstrap
- Figma/Avacode
- Wordpress, Shopware 6, TWIG
- Mobile first approach
- Adaptive layout techniques
- Icon font's
- React (self-learning in progress)

LANGUAGES

• English - intermediate

EDUCATION

GRADUATE

Hillel it school, Dnipro (2020-2021)

- Front-End Basic, Excellent grade
- Front-End Pro, Excellent grade

LAWYER

Dnipropetrovsk State University of Internal Affairs (2010 - 2015)